A single night. A million possibilities. One connection.
You Instead is a music, romance, comedy film directed by David Mackenzie.
Two feuding rock stars get handcuffed together for 24 hours at a
music festival where they are both due to perform.
Adam, played by Luke Treadaway.
Morello, played by Natalia Tena.
Tyko, played by Mathew Baynton.
Lake, played by Ruta Gedmintas.
Kim, played by Sophie Wu.
Lucie, played by Rebecca Benson.
You Instead (alternate U.S.
title Tonight You're Mine) is a 2011 British romantic comedy" written
by Thomas Leveritt and directed by David Mackenzie.
The film stars Luke Treadaway, Natalia Tena, Gavin
Mitchell and Alastair Mackenzie.
Set at T in the Park music festival and shot by Sigma Films, two feuding rock stars
are handcuffed together at a festival where they are due to perform.
The film explores themes of pop star, music festival, handcuffed.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.